(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T23:25:39.602753",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
僕たちは配信アプリ
We are on the streaming app...
ホロキャスで活動する配信者！
...Holocast, active as streamers!
突然画面に吸い込まれて
Suddenly sucked into the screen,
アプリと繋がる謎の世界、ホロキャス界に来ちゃった！
we ended up in Holocast Realm, a mysterious world connected to the app!
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象...
There, a phenomenon where the souls of those suffering in reality turn into monsters...
ユメオチが起こっていた！
...Yumeochi, was occurring.
怪物コラプサーを倒して
We must defeat the monster Collapsers
みんなの魂を取り戻さないと！
and take back everyone's souls!
そして、魔法少女に変身して戦うことになった。
And so, we ended up transforming into magical girls to fight.
みんなの心を助けて
Saving everyone's hearts
夢を応援する！
and supporting their dreams!
それが、
That is...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girl Holowitch!
今日はスペシャルハロウィーンステージ！
Today is the Special Halloween Stage!
ホロキャスの人気配信者が多数出演！
Many popular Holocast streamers are appearing!
さらに！今をときめく超人気歌手のカノンさんも参加する...
And! The super popular, rising singer Kanon-san will also participate...
...超超豪華イベント！
...in this super ultra-luxurious event!
で、その超豪華イベントのオープニングアクトを、うち等6人が担当することになって！
And we six are in charge of the opening act for that super luxurious event!
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着て、ドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかなーって！
Since it's a special occasion, I thought we'd all wear our Holowitch outfits and liven things up with a big bang!
でもいいのかな？魔法とか妖精とか... pride
But is that okay? Magic and fairies...
...一応内緒なんだけど...
...are supposed to be a secret, though...
今日はハロウィーンだから、仮装ってことにすれば...
Since today is Halloween, if we just call them costumes...
...何とかなるなる！
...it'll all work out!
そうそう！
Right, right!
って、そろそろ準備した方が良くない？
But shouldn't we get ready soon?
そうだね！
Yeah!
じゃ、気合い入れていきますか！
Alright, let's fire ourselves up!
トリック・オア...
Trick or...
...トリート！
...Treat!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー
Obsession, obsession, obsession...
足りないでしょ？
...it's not enough, is it?
こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Come over here, let's play!
イライラして
Feeling frustrated,
feeling frustrated,
楽しくいられるための勉強
studying how to stay happy!
イライラしてたら
If you keep being frustrated,
魂抜ける もったいない
your soul will escape, what a waste!
どうしたら喜んでくれるかな？ さあさあ
What can I do to make you happy? Come on, come on!
思いついては即行動
Once I think of it, I act immediately!
スマイルハンター
Smile Hunter!
こっそり君のツボをインプット
Secretly inputting your sweet spot,
お気に入りの衣装で行こう
let's go in our favorite outfits!
魔法だもん 愛の呪文フルキャスト
Because it's magic, a full cast of love spells!
とおー！
Go!
コンサート！
Concert!
まだまだ仕掛けちゃえ
Let's keep playing more tricks!
あっという間に捕まえた
Caught you in the blink of an eye!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーシンドローム
Obsession, obsession, Obsession Syndrome!
いたずらからのハピネス
Happiness born from mischief!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーしたでしょ？
You're obsessed, obsessed, obsessed now, aren't you?
照れ隠しです スマイルに
Warding off embarrassment with a smile!
年中無休カーニバル
A 365-day carnival!
好きが重なれば
If our love piles up,
魔法少女 ホロウィッチ！ THE STAGE ~TRICK or MAGIC!~
[Title: Magical Girl Holowitch! THE STAGE ~TRICK or MAGIC!~]
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or Treat!
みんな、盛り上がってるー？
Everyone, are you excited?
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト、どうだったー？
How was Holowitch's opening act?
ここからはもっともっともっと盛り上げていくから！
We're going to make things even more exciting from here on!
みんなと一緒に楽しもうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日は我々ホロキャスの配信者だけではなく
Today, we aren't the only ones streaming on Holocast...
あの超人気歌手、カノンさんがゲストで来てくださっていまーす！
The super popular singer, Kanon, is here as our guest!
カノンさん、どうぞー！
Please welcome, Kanon!
トリック・オア・トリート
Trick or treat.
みんな、今日は最後までよろしく
Everyone, I look forward to your support until the very end.
いやまさかね、あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるなんて！
I can't believe we're standing on the same stage as Kanon!
いや本当、憧れですよ！
Yes, really! She's such an inspiration!
カノンさんの歌を聴くと、すっごくパワーもらえるのら！
Listening to Kanon's songs gives me so much power!
そうそう！こんなにいただいちゃっていいんですか？ってくらいね
Right! To the point of thinking, "Is it really okay to get this much?"
うんうん、めっちゃ元気でるよね！
Yeah, it really cheers you up!
ありがとう、なんでもないから
Thank you. It's nothing.
次の曲は、みんなも一緒に歌ってほしいのら！
I want everyone to sing along for the next song!
キミたち！遠慮しないで声出してね！声！
Don't hold back, everyone! Let me hear your voices!
じょいふる
[Song: Joyful]
キミの声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ 冒険してみてない？
Come on, why don't we have an adventure?
楽しいこと始めよう
Let's get the fun started
遊びたい
I wanna have fun,
絶対
absolutely!
とぅ たい！たい！たい！
To, tai! Tai! Tai!
I wanna
JOYと JOYと JOYと POPなベイベー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and my pop baby
JOYと JOYと JOYと HAPPYなピーパー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and some happy people
ヨワムシなんかじゃない
I'm no wimp
自信ありげにピースサイン
Here's a confident peace sign
キミの瞳にキスして
I wanna kiss your eyes
笑いたい
And smile,
絶対 とぅ たい！たい！たい！
absolutely! To, tai! Tai! Tai!
I wanna
JOYと JOYと JOYと 陽気なベイベー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and cheerful baby
JOYと JOYと JOYと HAPPYなSayイェー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and a happy 'say yeah'
君の心はそう もっと Do Do
Your heart, yeah, it wants to do do more
僕の心もそう いっそ Good Good
My heart does too, all the more good good
はじけてるんじゃない？ イッツ ジョイフル
Aren't you bouncing around? It's joyful
ぱぴぷぺぽ ばぶぅ〜 イェイ！
Pa pi pu pe po ba boo~ yeah!
JOYと JOYと JOYと POPなベイベー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and my pop baby
JOYと JOYと JOYと HAPPYなピーパー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and some happy people
ドキドキしちゃうの なんでだろ
Why am I so excited?
ズキズキしちゃうの なんでだろ
Why am I throbbing with pain?
この指にとまるのは どんな運命なんだ
What kind of destiny will halt at my finger?
ぜんぶしたいな
I want to do it all
じょいふるだって 終わっちゃう
It might be joyful, but it'll come to an end
エブリバディ いつか終わっちゃう
Everybody will eventually end
いつ いつも このトキ も
When? Always, right this second
最終形は きっと 修正なしで
Bet our final form won't need any corrections
どぅ we do we do we do do
Do, we do we do we do do
ぴ ぷ ぺ ぽ ぱ ぴ ぷ ぺ 痛いっ！とぅたいっ！
Pi pu pe po, pa pi pu pe, ow! To do! To do!
とぅたいっ！たい！たい！
To do! Tai! Tai!
I wanna JOYと JOYと JOYと 陽気なベイベー
I wanna joy, and joy, and joy, and cheerful baby
JOYと JOYと JOYと HAPPYなSayイェー
Joy, and joy, and joy, and a happy 'say yeah'
君の心はそう もっと Do Do
Your heart, yeah, it wants to do do more
僕の心もそう いっそ Good Good
My heart does too, all the more good good
はじけてるんじゃない？ イッツ ジョイフル
Aren't you bouncing around? It's joyful
ぱぴぷぺぽ ばぶぅ〜
Pa pi pu pe po ba boo~
JOY
みんな、一緒に歌ってくれて、ありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for singing along with us!
いや、良かったねー！
Man, that was amazing!
会場がね、一体になったって感じでね！
It really felt like the venue became one!
うん。
Yeah.
よかったよかった！
That's great, that's great!
テンション上がるわ、これ！
This really pumps me up!
さ、さ、次は、いよいよ、カノンさんに歌っていただきます！
N-Now, next up, we'll finally have Kanon sing for us!
君、大丈夫？
Are you okay?
あ！何！？
Ah! What is that?!
何？何？
What? What's going on?
え？えええ！？
Huh? What?!
あわ、あわわって･･･
Bubble, bubbles...?
まさか！
No way!
あっ！
Ah!
うわっ！
Woah!
取れないんだけど！何これ！
I can't get it off! What is this?!
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょー！何？何？どういうこと？
W-W-Wait a minute! What? What? What's going on?!
コラプサーだ！
It's a Collapser!
ですよね！どう考えてもね！
I knew it! No matter how you look at it!
コラプサー･･･やっぱり。
A Collapser... Just as I thought.
うわー！
Whoa!
んんん･･･
Ugh...
はず、れ･･･ぬ、ぬ、抜けない！
It won't... c-come off!
わるっ！
Take that!
怖い、怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary, scary!
えっと、えっと、こういう時は！
Um, um, in times like this!
ト、トリック・オア・トリート！
T-Trick or Treat!
何もかも違うだろ！
Everything about that is wrong!
うわっ、えいっ！
Whoa, take this!
うぅ･･･うわぁぁぁ！
Ugh... Noooo!
フブキ先輩！前後が逆になってるよ！
Fubuki-senpai! You're upside down!
フブキ先輩！うわぁぁ！
Fubuki-senpai! Whoa!
フブキ先輩、出てる出てる！楽しいのモツが出てる！
Fubuki-senpai, it's coming out! Your happy soul is coming out!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
うぅ･･･。だが、コラプサーが出てくるってことは･･･
Ugh... But if a Collapser is appearing here...
夢落ちしてる人がいるんだ。多分。
Someone must be falling into a Dream Sink. Probably.
ミオ先輩！
Mio-senpai!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
ご、ごめん･･･うち、うち、本当は･･･
I-I'm sorry... I, I actually...
ハロウィンのカボチャが、怖くてダメなの！
I'm so terrified of Halloween pumpkins!
えっ！？
What?!
小さい頃、パパがハロウィンで･･･
When I was little, on Halloween, my dad...
あれ、被って帰ってきて･･･
wore one of those on his head when he came home...
うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって思っちゃって･･･
and I thought my dad had been eaten by the pumpkin...
ハッピーハロウィーン!!
Happy Halloween!!
それから、どうしても･･･
Since then, no matter what I do...
ハロウィンのカボチャだけは、無理なのー！
I just can't handle Halloween pumpkins!
何？
What is that?
いやーー！！
Noooo!!
チェンジ！
Transform!
ガーディアンアーム！
Guardian Arm!
巫女メロポンポン！
Miko Mero Pom-pom!
ロリポップ・キャンディー・パラソル！
Lollipop Candy Parasol!
ガンバリナ！
Ganbarina!
スノーフレークセイバー！
Snowflake Saber!
切り裂き丸！
Kirisakimaru!
ここは任せて、ミオ！
Leave this to us, Mio!
みんな･･･
Everyone...
魔法、みんなに見せちゃうけど、いいよね！
We're going to show everyone our magic, okay?
うん、そんなこと言ってられないし！
Yeah, we don't have time to hesitate!
だよね！夢落ちした人を助ける、それが･･･
Right! Saving people who fall into the Dream Sink is what...
魔法少女、ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girls, HoloWitch!
この手を差し伸べ･･･
Reach out this hand...
掴んで、握る！
grab onto it, and hold tight!
天使のホロ、魔法少女かなた！
Angel's Holo, Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り！
A prayer to make everyone's wishes bloom!
巫女のホロ、魔法少女みこ！
Shrine Maiden's Holo, Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せ、お裾分け！
Sharing a taste of sweet happiness!
姫のホロ、魔法少女るーな！
Princess's Holo, Magical Girl Luna!
煌めくお宝、ロックオン！
Sparkling treasure, locked on!
海賊のホロ、魔法少女マリン！
Pirate's Holo, Magical Girl Marine!
心躍らすトリックスター！
The heart-racing trickster!
狐のホロ、魔法少女フブキ！
Fox's Holo, Magical Girl Fubuki!
積もり重なる純白の愛
The accumulating pure white love,
雪のホロ
The Holo of Snow,
魔法少女ラミィ！
Magical Girl Lamy!
ホロウィッチ、
HoloWitch,
クルセイド！
Crusade!
いくよー！
Here I go!
ほいっ、そいっ、はい！
Hup, step, yah!
パンプキン敵じゃないよ
Pumpkins are no match for us!
ばかばかだよ
They're so silly.
コン！
Kon!
やめな！
Stop it!
せいっ！
Hah!
は、はわ、はわわー
H-H-Help...
うわ、うわ、うわ、うわー
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
うぅっ！
Ugh!
な、なんかこれ、まずくない？
Th-this is getting bad, isn't it?
どんどん強くなってる！
It's getting stronger and stronger!
みんなが奴らを倒すより、
At this rate, before we can even defeat them...
不安と恐れが膨れ上がる方が早いみたい！
their fear and anxiety will grow even faster!
そ、そんな！
N-No way!
うちのせい...
It's my fault...
うちが...
Because I...
あんなもの怖いって思っちゃうせいで...
Because I thought those things were scary...
そんなこと...
That's not true...
分かってるの。
I know it is.
おかしいよね、あんなのが...
It's weird, isn't it? To find something like that...
こんな、どうしようもなく怖いなんて。
so incredibly terrifying.
だから、
That's why...
今日も我慢して、
I wanted to hold it in today...
頑張ろうって、
and do my best,
思ったのに...
is what I thought...
でも...
But...
でも、やっぱり！
But I just can't!
おかしくなんてないよ。
There's nothing weird about it.
カノンさん...
Kanon-san...
誰にだって、
Everyone...
苦手なものがある。
has something they aren't good at.
怖いもの、
Things they fear,
嫌いなもの。
things they hate.
人に「なんでそんなものが」って言われても、
Even if people ask, "Why are you afraid of that?"
どうしようもないことって、
there are just some things...
やっぱりあるよ。
you can't help but feel.
そうだよ！
That's right!
何が苦手とか、何が怖いかとかは関係なくて、
It doesn't matter what you're bad at or what you fear.
大事なのは、
What matters is...
今、ミオちゃんが辛いって思ってることどうかだから！
how much Mio-chan is suffering right now!
遠慮しないで、
Don't hold back,
頼ってほしいのら！
we want you to lean on us!
だって、そういうのさ、
After all, in times like these,
うちら、お互い様じゃん！
we're in this together!
誰かの辛さや誰かの苦手は、ほかの誰かがカバーする。
Someone's pain or weakness can be covered by someone else.
お互いそうやって、
That's how we've always...
やってきたから、
gotten through it,
今だって、
and even now,
こんなに頑張れる！
we can fight this hard!
みんな...
Everyone...
ホロウィッチ、
HoloWitch,
コラプサーは、
the Collapsar is...
夢落ちした人の恐れと不安から生まれ、
born from the fears and anxiety of those who fall into Nightmare.
その心を深く沈ませていく。
It drags their hearts deep into the abyss.
夢落ちって...
Fall into Nightmare...
どうしてそれを......
How do you know that...?
でも、私は知っている。
But I know this.
君たちなら、
If it's you,
ホロウィッチなら。
if you are HoloWitch.
辛い、苦しい、悲しい、きつい。
Painful, agonizing, sad, tough.
そんな、自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中にいても、
Even in the darkness you cannot escape on your own,
夢に、光を届けてくれる。
you will deliver light to their dreams.
任せて！
Leave it to us!
さあ、みんな。
Now, everyone.
ホロウィッチが戦ってくれる。
HoloWitch is fighting for us.
では、私たちにできるのは？
So, what is it that we can do?
そう、私たちの声で、思いで、
Yes, with our voices and our feelings,
彼女たちを応援することだ！
we can cheer them on!
いざ、トリック・オア・トリート！
Now, Trick or Treat!
あれよという間に飲み込まれる
In the blink of an eye, you're swallowed up
橙色のタイダルウェイヴ
by an orange tidal wave,
夜行夜光
glowing in the night march.
ハンドメイドからオーダーメイドまで仕掛ける大流行
Spreading a massive craze, from handmade to custom-made
本物から偽物までまとめて大集合
Gathering everything together, from the real to the fake
揃いも揃って不揃いの世界観に
All lined up in a mismatched worldview,
お揃いの幼稚さに辟易な恒例
weary of the same old childish traditions.
催しの一夜漬け 夜通し踊れ
A makeshift overnight festival, dance all night long!
条例処刑フォーメーションで褒美を獲れ
Win your reward with the regulation execution formation!
マーマレードが溶ける頃
By the time the marmalade melts,
キャパ以上にお道化る者
clown around beyond your capacity.
チヤホヤしたりされたりがいいんでしょ？
Isn't it nice to pamper and be pampered?
甘いだけ じゃ物足りない give me some more
Just being sweet is not enough, give me some more!
チェック it 刺激的ヒステリーベイビー
Check it, sensational hysteric baby!
無限に艶美 sensitive
Infinitely charming and sensitive.
何でもかんでも制御不能
Everything is out of control!
ビビディ・バビディ・エギ・マイナス・エギ・バイタル
Bibbidi-bobbidi-egi-minus-egi-vital
ウニカ・ウニサス・イニ・ミニ・マニ・マモ
Unica Unisas Ini Mini Mani Mo!
恐ろしや そろそろ
How scary, it's about time...
光り上がり舞う月に針が落ちるわ
The needle falls on the moon dancing up in light.
大きなくちばしで笑うカボチャたち
Pumpkins laughing with wide mouths.
それが合図 魔物たちが目覚め躍る
That's the signal, monsters awaken and dance.
こうなればあとは 思いのまま
Once it's like this, the rest is as we wish.
ホロウ 骨抜きダンスサバト
Hollow, bone-melting dance sabbat!
スケアクロウも 飛び跳ね回る
Even the scarecrow leaps and bounds about.
ホロウ 月夜のダンスデポ
Hollow, moonlit dance depot!
くるくるくる 押し寄せ回り ウィーガッタパーティーナイト
Spin, spin, spin, crowding and swirling,
we got a party night!
Anyway, enjoy the party night!
ナイナイナイ
No, no, no!
わいえいわいえい ルキミナプープー ジャッキナプーキジョムリ
Y-A-Y, Y-A-Y, look at me now poo-poo,
Jack-in-a-pooky, no way!
サタクサタクはジェイソンナシで トテトテのヘラヘラゲラゲラヘーヤ
Satac Satac without Jason,
tottering, flippant, laughing away, hey-yah!
ワンス・モア 素敵なナイト 見つからなくても ステディ・バライル
Once more, a wonderful night,
even if you can't find it, steady barile!
転がりおちるガタキテルミ シマテからハイドキルリギルギル
Rolling down, rattling,
hide and kill from the inside out.
よっぴー! 有無の衣装も爪先の刃
Yoppy! Yes-or-no costumes and blades on our toes.
丸ごとのファミリアに仕留めたちなりジャンジャン
Bringing down the entire familiar, clang clang!
ガラパゴスに交わる異世界 大混乱パーティー
Merging in the Galapagos, another world,
absolute chaos party!
振り切れる鼓動
The heartbeat swinging wide!
哀れな街のドラキュラ お酒を煽る
The Dracula of this pitiful town, chugging down alcohol.
寡黙そうなデュラハン 頭を振る
The silent-looking Dullahan shakes his head.
紳士的なミイラすら 服がはだける
Even the gentlemanly mummy gets his clothes disheveled.
どあれど愉快 全開のまんま
However it is, we keep the joy in full throttle!
本性 あらわに暴れよう
Let's run wild, revealing our true natures!
その仮装も正装になる
That costume, too, will become formal wear!
狂騒曲のダンスデポ
The Rhapsody's dance depot!
あいたた 押し寄せ回り ウィーガッタパーティーナイト
Ouch, crowding and swirling, we got a party night!
ハイファイ オールナイト 眠れやしない
High-five all night, there's no sleeping!
オーライ ラララララ
All right, la-la-la-la-la!
フライハイ オールナイト 鳴りやまない
Fly high all night, it won't stop ringing!
オーライ ラララララ
All right, la-la-la-la-la!
孤独な夜遊び
Lonely night play.
ランタンはまるで魂
The lantern is like a soul.
奇怪なジャンボリー
A strange jamboree.
泣き出してハロウィン
Bursting into tears on Halloween.
ホロウ 骨抜きダンスサバト
Hollow, bone-melting dance sabbat!
スケアクロウも 飛び跳ね回る
Even the scarecrow leaps and bounds about.
ホロウ 月夜のダンスデポ
Hollow, moonlit dance depot!
くるくるくる 押し寄せ回り ウィーガッタパーティーナイト
Spin, spin, spin, crowding and swirling,
we got a party night!
Anyway, enjoy the party night!
くるくるくる 押し寄せ回り ウィーガッタパーティーナイト
Spin, spin, spin, crowding and swirling,
we got a party night!
ナイナイナイ
No, no, no!
コサックの力が乱れてる！
Kossacks' power is going wild!
恐れと不安が溶けていくんだ… 歌の力…
My fear and anxiety are melting away...
The power of song...
ふふっ、みんなの声の力で！
Hehe, with the power of everyone's voices!
みんな乗ってるね！
Everyone's grooving!
おかげでこっちもやる気いっぱいなのだ！
Thanks to that, I'm fully motivated too!
さあ、行って。ホロウィッチ。心を苛むトリックに…
Now, go, Holowitch.
Against the tricks that plague our hearts...
とびきりのトリート！
A top-tier treat!
はっ！
Yah!
みんな、応援ありがとう！
Everyone, thanks for the support!
思う存分、楽しんじゃうよ！
I'm going to enjoy this to the fullest!
トリック・イット！
Trick it!
わぁ〜 やられた〜
Whoa, they got me!
やぁー！
Yah!
はっ！
Ha!
いぇーい！
Yay!
イノセント・リバイバー！
Innocent Reviver!
ぷはぁ〜
Phew~
お？
Oh?
信じるからね。みんなの愛が、力をくれる！
I believe in it. Everyone's love gives me strength!
はっ！ おりゃー！
Ha! Take this!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
ラミィちゃん、ナイス！
Lamy-chan, nice!
それじゃあ、決めちゃうよ！
Alright, let's finish this!
はぁー！
Haaah!
こん！
Kon!
ふっ！
Ha!
ユニ・ラミネーション・スラッシュ・ストーム・コンプレックス！
Uni-Lamination Slash Storm Complex!
はっ！ れいやー！
Ha! Reiyah!
ふっ
Hmph!
イェーイ！
Yay!
みこみこジャパン！
Miko-Miko Japan!
サンキューんなたん！
Thank you, Nnatan!
うおーーー！
Uohhh!
しゃー！
Sha!
たーーー！
Tahhh!
おるぁー！
Orya!
あっ
Ah!
下がって！
Get back!
ペイパースフィア！
Paper Sphere!
みんなみこのエリートなとこ
You all want to see my elite side
そんなに見たいんだ
so badly, huh?
しょうがないね！
I guess I have no choice!
みんなと一緒に！
With everyone!
ルナ・マギカ・ルナ！
Luna Magica Luna!
セイバー・サクラ・ブルーム・セイバー！
Saber Sakura Bloom Saber!
プリンセス・プリン！
Princess Purin!
ふん！
Humph!
はっ
Ha!
スラッシュ・ヘイロー！
Slash Halo!
はぁー！
Haa!
はっ
Ha!
マリン、行くよ！
Marine, let's go!
サンキューかなたん
Thank you, Kanatan.
てーー！
Fire!
みんなの想い
With everyone's feelings
全部乗っけて
backing us up,
飛び込んでいくしかねぇだろ！
we have no choice but to dive right in!
君たち、カード欲しい時に来てくれるじゃん。
You guys come right when we need a card.
みんな揃って、いいお宝ね。
Together, you're quite the treasure.
よっしゃー！
Yes!
やーーー！
Yahhh!
セレスティアル・リンキング！
Celestial Linking!
オーヴァースプラッシュゲイル！
Over Splash Gale!
あいつらでラストだ！
That's the last of them!
決めるよ、みんな！
Let's finish this, everyone!
チェンジ！ホロウィッチステッキ！
Change! Holowitch Wand!
ウィッチ・ドラム！
Witch Drum!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
ミオ先輩、もう大丈夫そう？
Mio-senpai, are you okay now?
あ、うん。
Ah, yeah.
その、見ないようにすればなんとか。
Um, as long as I don't look down, I'm okay somehow.
わかるよ。白上も高いところ行くと下見れないからね。
I understand. Shirakami can't look down when going to high places either.
んなたんもー！
Nnatan too!
虫はなるべく見ないようにしてるのら。
I try not to look at bugs as much as possible-nora.
ありがとう、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに、
Just like everyone helped me,
うちも、みんなが辛い時、
if there's ever a hard time
苦しい時があったら、
or a painful time for any of you...
絶対、絶対に力になるから！
I will absolutely, absolutely be there to help!
さて、これでめでたしめでたし。でもいいんだけど...
Now then, living happily ever after would be nice, but...
みんな！ホロウィッチの活躍、もっと見たいんじゃない？
Everyone! Don't you want to see more of HoloWitch in action?
だそうだけど...
That's what they say...
いやあああ！
Nooo!
え？こっち？こっち振るの？
Wait, me? You're passing it to me?
え？あ、や...
Eh? Uh, no...
やります！
I'll do it!
よし、やるよ、みんな！
Alright, let's do this, everyone!
おー！
Yeah!
RPG
[Song: RPG]
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to be scared of, we're no longer alone.
大切な何かが壊れたあの夜に
On that night when something important broke,
僕は星を探して一人で歩いていた
I was walking alone, looking for the stars.
ペルセウス座流星群 君も見てただろうか
The Perseid meteor shower... Were you looking at it too?
僕は元気でやってるよ
I'm doing fine,
君は今「ドコ」にいるの？
where are you right now?
「方法」という悪魔にとり憑かれないで
Don't be possessed by the devil called "method,"
「目的」という大事なものを思い出して<
remember the important thing called "purpose."
おーおー
Oh, oh!
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to be scared of, we're no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
It's okay to be scared, we're no longer alone.
大切な何かが壊れたあの夜に
On that night when something important broke,
僕は君を探して一人で歩いていた
I was walking alone, looking for you.
あの日から僕らは一人で海を目指す
Since that day, we've been heading for the sea alone.
「約束のあの場所で必ずまた逢おう。」と
Saying, "We'll definitely meet again at that promised place."
「世間」という悪魔に惑わされないで
Don't be fooled by the devil called "society,"
自分だけが決めた「答」を思い出して<
remember the "answer" that you decided on by yourself.
おーおー
Oh, oh!
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to be scared of, we're no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
It's okay to be scared, we're no longer alone.
”煌めき”のような人生の中で
In a life that's like a sparkle,
君に出逢えて僕は本当によかった
I'm really glad I met you.
街を抜け海に出たら 次はどこを目指そうか
When we leave the city and head to the sea, where should we head next?
僕らはまた出かけよう 愛しいこの地球を
Let's go out again, to this beloved world.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There is nothing to fear,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk toward the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
Even if you are afraid, it's okay,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we are no longer alone.
みんな、今日はありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね、みんな！
It was the absolute most fun Halloween, right, everyone?!
ふふっ、ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ、そういうのも含めて...
Hehe, although we had a few accidents, including those things...
いいお宝になったんじゃない？
hasn't it become a wonderful treasure?
そうだー！
That's right!
いいお宝
[Text: Great Treasure]
おもいで
[Text: Memories]
おっ...
Oh...
さて、そろそろお時間となってまいりましたが...
Well, it is about time for us to wrap up, but...
アンコール！
Encore!
それじゃあ、アンコールにお応えして！
Well then, in response to your encore!
この曲、歌っちゃうのら！
We're going to sing this song, nora!
はじまりの魔法-charm-
The Magic of Beginnings -charm-!
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
引き寄せるのよ奇跡
and draw miracles close to us.
始まりを告げる 鐘の音が響く
The sound of the bell signaling the beginning echoes,
気付いた時がいつだって スタートラインなんだ
whenever you realize it, that's your starting line.
何者でもなかった 君を変えたのは
What changed you when you were nobody
見つけたばかりの小さな冒険の輝き 磨け 宝石
is the shine of a small adventure you just found—polish it, jewel!
どうして私だけ うまくいかないんだろう
Why is it only me who can't do things right?
自分以外のすべてが 眩しく見えるけど<
Everything except myself looks so dazzling,
ねえ 君に
hey, to you...
見つけてほしくて
I want to be found.
なりたい私になる 今こそ
I'll become who I want to be, starting right now!
そうだ 叶えたい 掴みたい 夢があるから
Yes, because I have a dream I want to fulfill and grasp,
塞ぎ込んだ昨日の言葉 連れて 踏み出すんだ
taking yesterday's downcast words with me, I will take a step forward!
信じる力が 奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief may bring about miracles,
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
引き寄せるのよ奇跡
and draw miracles close to us.
高鳴る望みと
With rising expectations
変わらない願い
and unchanging wishes,
それぞれが等しく 流れていく世界で
in a world where each one flows equally,
何を求めて 歩き続けてるんだろう
what is it we seek as we keep on walking?
君がくれたこの空が
This sky that you gave me...
消えない 翼をくれたね
It gave me wings that will never disappear.
そうだ 照らしたい 届けたい 人がいるから
Yes, because there's someone I want to shine upon and reach,
もう一人置いていったりしないと 決めたんだ
I've decided I won't leave anyone behind again.
愛したい 応えたい 自分自身の声
I want to love and answer my own inner voice.
正解なんてこれからの 未体験のステージ
The right answer lies in the yet-unexperienced stage ahead.
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine,
どんな姿でもいい
and any form is fine.
追いかけたいんだ あのきらめきを
I want to chase after that sparkle!
希望も 光も 力も すべて
Hope, light, and power—everything,
抱きしめて持っていこう
let's embrace it all and bring it with us!
ほら 繋げたい 広げたい 道があるから
Look, because there is a path we want to connect and expand,
ここから始まる物語を 一緒にいこう
let's go together on the story that starts from here!
信じる力が 奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief may bring about miracles...
繋ぐ手と右手
Hand in hand...
ひとりじゃないから
...you are not alone.
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you.
We can spell all your dreams
最高のステージだったよ、ホロウィッチ！
That was the best stage, HoloWitches!
本当、本当！
Totally, totally!
みんな、お疲れ様！
Good job, everyone!
カノンさん、あの...
Mr. Canon, um...
今日は本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today!
それで、あなたはどうして夢堕ちとか僕たちのことを？
But why do you know about Dreamfallen and us?
私、前に夢堕ちして...
I once became Dreamfallen...
君たちに助けられたことがあるんだ。
...and was saved by you all.
ええっ？
Really?!
だから、あの時の自分と同じように、
So, just like how I was back then,
夢堕ちして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると、放っておけなくて。
when I see someone suffering as a Dreamfallen, I can't ignore them.
あと、実は...
And actually...
今日このステージに出ることにしたのも、
the reason I decided to perform on this stage today...
君たちが出るって聞いたからなんだ。
...is because I heard that you all would be here.
もう一度会えたら、って思って。
I wanted to see you again.
だから今日は、えっと...
So today, um...
すごく嬉しかった！
...I was really happy!
これからも頑張ってね、ホロウィッチ！
Keep doing your best, HoloWitches!
それじゃ！
Well then!
また！ぜひまた！
See you! We must meet again!
あの人自身が夢堕ちしてホロウィッチに助けられていたから、
Since he himself was once Dreamfallen and saved by HoloWitches,
知っていたんだ。夢堕ちした時の辛さも、
he understood. He knew how painful it is to be Dreamfallen,
そんな時、誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも。
and how joyful it is when someone reaches out their hand.
そっか。みこたちが、少しでも誰かの力になれたら、
I see. If we can be of help to someone, even a little bit...
その誰かが、また別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね。
...then that person can help someone else in return.
そうだね。
That's right.
しかもさ、それだけじゃなくて、うちらの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん。
Besides, that's not all. They also become our source of strength, too.
あの人や、今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに。
Just like him, and everyone who supported us today.
それって...
That means...
それってすっごく...
That is super...
すっごくトリート！
Super Treat!
キラキラ 星みたいに輝いている
Shining brightly, just like a twinkling star,
夢の結晶 みんなの宝物
the crystal of dreams is everyone's treasure.
ときどき 見失っちゃうこともあるけど
Though there are times we lose sight of it,
あふれだした 光が僕を呼ぶんだよ
the overflowing light is calling out to me.
絶対大丈夫 ただまっすぐで
You'll definitely be fine. Just being honest...
何度も立ち上がる 君と一緒に進んでく
Standing up again and again, moving forward with you.
夢は 夢は まだ終わらない
Our dreams... our dreams are not over yet!
未来をとり戻そう
Let's reclaim our future.
何度だって笑って もう一歩歩き始めよう
Let's smile as many times as it takes and take another step.
ホロウィッチ、オン・ユア・サイド
HoloWitch, on your side!
夢の先へ
Toward the beyond of dreams!
ワクワクするような日々 夢の結晶
Exciting days, the crystal of dreams...
思い出して 魔法を唱えてみたら
if you remember them and cast a spell...
ドキドキするような 君の物語
...a heart-pounding story of yours...
もう一度...
...will begin once more.
きらり光り出す物語
...a glittering story begins.
頑張ってみても
Even if you try your best,
うまくいかない日のほうが多く感じちゃったりするよね
it feels like there are more days when things don't go well, right?
不安や悲しみも
With all the anxiety and sadness,
抱えないで 一人じゃない
don't keep them to yourself; you're not alone.
希望の種を明日に蒔いたら
If you sow the seeds of hope for tomorrow,
一番に輝く 綺麗な花が咲くよ
the most beautiful flower will bloom, shining the brightest.
夢を歌おう 魔法に乗せて
Let's sing our dreams, carrying them on magic.
何度だって踊ろう 君と一緒に進んでく
Let's dance again and again, moving forward with you.
夢は 夢は まだ終わらない
Our dreams, our dreams are not over yet,
未来を取り戻そう
so let's reclaim the future.
何度だって
Again and again...
笑って もう一回 歩き始めよう
...laughing, let's start walking once more.
ホロウィッチ おやすみ 夢の先へ
Holowitches, good night, to the end of the dream.